{
    "subject": "resource/Karipey_Rural_District",
    "predicate": "ontology/isPartOf",
    "object": "resource/Babol_County",
    "human_readable": "Karipey Rural District is part of Babol County.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9702268838882446,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Karipey Rural District and Babol County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9696598649024963,
            "question": "What county is Karipey Rural District part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9356839656829834,
            "question": "Is there a town called Karipey in Babol County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9182271361351013,
            "question": "Where is Karipey Rural District located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9178791642189026,
            "question": "How might living in Karipey Rural District be different from living in a city within Babol County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8823784589767456,
            "question": "Are there cities within Karipey Rural District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8706862926483154,
            "question": "What type of area is Karipey Rural District?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8118108510971069,
            "question": "Can you name any other rural districts in Babol County?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6312135457992554,
            "question": "What are some of the characteristics of rural districts like Karipey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45931679010391235,
            "question": "Is Babol County a region or administrative division?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karipey Rural District is part of Babol County.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6497_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the characteristics of rural districts like Karipey?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6497_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other rural districts in Babol County?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6497_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of area is Karipey Rural District?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6497_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6497_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The document for file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6497/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt mentions that Karipey Rural District is located in Babol County, Mazandaran Province, Iran."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that Karipey Rural District is part of Babol County, as explicitly stated in one of the text snippets."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}